六年来，我们发现，
What we are finding in the six years
在全国各地与这些了不起的人
that we've been doing courage to teach retreats
一起参与教学勇气静修会，
with these amazing folk around the country
有一些可以确定的
is that there are nameable definable outcomes
有形结果...
in the forms of...
首先，学生认为这些教师的教学
first of all, students perceiving these teachers as
更多来自他们自己，
teaching more from who they are,
为学习创造更多好客的课堂空间，
creating more hospitable classroom spaces for learning
因为教师自己在他们的
because the teachers themselves are
角色中更自在，
more at home in their role and
更能够看到学生的心，
more able to see the heart of the student
因为他们在看到自己的心方面得到了帮助。
having had help in seeing their own hearts.
所以,在最重要的方面，
So they become better teachers,
即忠实和良好地服务于
in the most important way that counts,
年轻人的生活的能力，
the capacity to serve the
他们成为更好的教师。
life of a young person faithfully and  well.
如果我有机会在一个非常大的
If I had a chance to address
大厅里对满是萎靡不振的教师讲话，
a very large hall full of dispirited teachers,
我首先想说的是:
I'd first want to say this:
我知道，你们所有人都是
I know that all of you came into teaching
通过心灵的运动进入教学领域的，
through a movement of the heart,
你们想把自己的心交给世界；
you wanted to give your heart to the world.
我知道你们在这里，
I know that you're all here now
因为我们周围和内心的环境
because conditions around us and inside of us
让我们失去了信心。
caused us to lose heart.
我想让你们会回答的问题是,
The question I want you to ask is,
“有没有一种方法可以让你们重新振作起来，
"Is there a way to take heart again,
以便你们可以再次做
so that you can once more do what
优秀教师一直在做的事情，
good teachers always do,
那就是把心交给他们的学生”。
which is to give heart to their students".
我想说的是，这个问题有一个答案。
And I'd want  to say there's an answer to that question.
我已经亲眼看到了这一点，
And I've seen it with my own eyes,
它就在我在全国各地
it's in the colleagues of yours whom I've met
遇到的你的同事身上，
around the country from inner-city
从巴尔的摩到沃斯堡，从德克萨斯到英国，
Baltimore to Fort Worth Texas to Britons
从卡罗莱纳州到西雅图，
necks out Carolina to Seattle to
到新墨西哥州的阿尔伯克基。
Albuquerque New Mexico.
同事们正以社区的
Colleagues who are coming together
形式走到一起。
in forms of community.
我亲眼看到，
I've seen with my own eyes,
全国各地的老师聚在一起，
teachers around the country coming together
致力于培养任何人类最终
committing to cultivating the only source of power
拥有的唯一力量源泉，
any human being ultimately has,
那就是心灵的力量，
which is the power of the heart,
灵魂和精神的力量。
the power  of the soul and the spirit.
而在由教师同伴组成的社区中这样做，
And doing that in communities of fellow teachers
可以帮助他们倾听内心的声音,
who can help them listen to their hearts,
让他们对所听到的东西保持诚实，
keep them honest about what they're hearing
并采取下一步措施，
and take next steps towards
重拾教学勇气。
regaining the courage to teach.